ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4194
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files
1973-1997
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
McKersie, Robert B.
Doherty, Robert E.
Rehmus, Charles M.
Lipsky, David B.
Lawler, Edward J.
Smith, Robert S.
/4194
7 cubic feet
7 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8051168
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 21, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 04, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4193: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files
McKersie, Robert B.; Doherty, Robert E.; Rehmus, Charles M.; Lipsky, David B., 1939-; Lawler, Edward J.; Smith, Robert S.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Dean's Office; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
8051168
- Statutory College Deans Meeting Documents, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Statutory College Deans Meeting Documents, 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- ILR Courses and Staff Documents, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Extension Division Annual Reports and Summaries, 1975-1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Program Studies, Statistics and Enrollment, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ILR Faculty Vita and Course Syllabi, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Extension and Public Service Reports, Critical Path Planning and Metropolitan District Programs, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Manual of Policies and Procedures, Division of Extension and Public Service, 1968-1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Scope and Contents
  Leather-bound binder
- Baruch-Cornell MILR Degree Program, 1982-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Cornell-Oxford Program, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Cornell-Baruch MSILR Program, 1982-1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Cornell-Baruch MSILR Program, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- ILR-Baruch Master's Degree Program, 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- ILR-Baruch Master's Degree Program, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Cornell-Baruch ILR Master's Degree Program, 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- "A Study of Metropolitan District Programs Past, Present, Future", 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  ILR School
- ILR Credit and Certificate Program Report, Report to the ILR Dean and Faculty, Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- "Resident Full Time Instructional Faculty Compensation and Public Service Overload Teaching" and Correspondence, 1980-1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- "resident Full Time Instructional Faculty Compensation for Extension and Public Service Overload Teaching", 1977-1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- "Reference Information for the 1994 Minimum Wage Advisory Panel" (Box 3, Folder 1)
  October 1994; New York State Department of Labor Division of Research and Statistics; Binder
- Human Services Administration, Ron House Papers, 1987-1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Employee Assistance Program (Trice, Foster, Sonenstuhl, etc.), 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Empire State College, 1988-1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Reports and Correspondence on the Empire State College, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- ILR and Empire State College Memorandums and Correspondence, 1971-1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Public Employees Federation Administration Documents, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Public Employees Federation, Public Service Training Program, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Public Employees Federation, Public Service Training Program, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Public Employees Federation, Training and Communication, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Public Employees Federation Administration, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Public Employees Federation, Public Service Training Program, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Public Employee Federation, Public Service Training Program, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Public Employee Federation, Public Sector Law and Practice, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- ILR Curriculum and Teachers, Public Employees Federation Public Sector Labor Studies, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Teleconference Public Employees Federation and the ILR, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  September 20 1989
- Last Folder (Box 4, Folder 14)
- ILR Center for Advanced Human Resources Studies, 1987-1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- The ILR Report, 1981-1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- CU-29-1, Oral History Project, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Affirmative Action and Women at Cornell, 1976-1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- CU-32-4, Staff and Employment Matters, 1975-1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- ILR-Baruch MSILR Degree Program, 1977-1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Joint Program in ILR Leading to a Master Degree between ILR and Baruch College, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Labor Education Newsletter Documents, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Labor Legacy Committee, Richard Strassberg, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Beth Israel Medical Center 1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- 50th Anniversary ILR Research Volume, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Cornell Labor Advisory Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Cornell Labor Advisory Committee, 1973-1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- ILR Extension Planning Committee, 1981-1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Extension Nominations and Elections Committee, 1981-1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Extension Personnel Committee, 1985-1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Extension and Nondegree Credit Program Committee, 1981-1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Extension Course Approval Committee, 1990-1995 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Extension Division Director's Meetings, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Syracuse, July 1, 1996; Syracuse, April 25, 1996
- Annual Reports and Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Cornell University Budget, 1994-1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Chronologically-organized E-Mails, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Documents, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- National Center for the Workplace Meetings, Governing Board, Site Directors, etc.), 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  April 1994; June 8 1994 November 16 1994; January 8 1995
- National Center for the Workplace Strategic and Operational Plan, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  June 1994
- Office of Sponsored Programs Agreement, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Original ILR Research Proposals, 1994-1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Quarterly Progress Reports, 1994-1994 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- NCW Research Plans, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  October and November 1994
- The Seeber and Olson Research Proposal, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Separate Proposals, Katz, Ehren, Blau and Kahn, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Seeber Site Reports, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- National Center for the Workplace Time Lines for Drafts, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- The National Center for the Workplace Vision Statement, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- National Center for the Workplace Miscellaneous Documents, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- National Center for the Workplace Documents, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 18)